[footsteps approaching]
[washing machine whirring]
All the machines are taken.
What are you doing?
Get your own.
[grunts]
[phone rings]
SARAH: This is Sarah.
You know what to do.
[phone beeps]
RIAN: Hey, babe.
Please just call me back. Okay?
I, I really miss you
and just please call me back.
Okay? Please?
[smooches]
Hey, Sarah.
I got insurance tickets
for Christmas.
I know how much you love it
and I figured
what better way to rekindle
that we're going
to a concert you love?
[phone beeps]
Sarah, it's been forever, okay?
Just shoot me
a text or something.
I just wanna know you're okay.
[phone beeps]
Remember that time
we went to Limp Bizkit
and I ended up
puking everywhere
and on your new shoes?
[laughs]
- Please call me back.
-[phone beeps]
Sarah, are you
fucking kidding me?
It takes 30 seconds
to answer, okay?
-This is getting ridiculous.
-[phone beeps]
You know what?
Ed Sheeran's
not even that good.
Actually, he sucks, and so,
does your taste in music.
-[phone beeps]
- Babe, I'm so sorry.
Please take me back.
Ed's the best in the world.
Okay. I didn't mean it.
-I promise
I'll never do that again.
-[phone beeps]
VOICE RECORD:
When you have
finished recording,
-you may hang up or press 1
for more options.
-[phone beep]
[reception bell]
[chiming continues]
EMILY: No! Give it back!
I hate you!
[loud thudding]
Is everything okay?
Stupid machine ate my money.
[sighs]
[machine beeps]
[clanking]
RIAN: Here.
I...
I'm not allowed
to take money from strangers.
[machine beeps]
Fuck. This is bullshit.
Yoshimi is so OP!
Best out of 15.
I should probably, like,
check-in and call my agent
and write that thing,
I got paid for.
Sorry.
Welcome.
What brings you
to the Claiborne?
Self-isolating.
I'm actually a writer.
Me too. What do you write?
Got a deadline due in a week,
and girlfriend just dumped me.
Just needed some distance
from it all, you know?
Sarah ghosted me anyway.
So, it's not like there was
really much closure, you know?
But it's kind of weird
wishing that we had, like,
a screaming match,
so that I could, like,
workshop my personality
or something, you know?
-We'll just need a credit card.
-Oh, yeah.
[footsteps]
Just, uh, looking for my room.
Why are you following me?
I'm not.
You literally are.
It's creepy.
I'm just looking for my room,
the same as you.
Okay.
So, where's your fucking room?
Ah, 2-- 226.
Back there. We passed it.
Would it be creepy
if the roles were rehearsed?
No. So, call me creep.
Don't take offense to my
self-preservation skills, creep.
Yeah. Good luck with those.
ZACH: I don't know
who you're talking to
on your phone.
-BRANDY: Who am I talking to?
-ZACH: In your, in your phone.
You're just like,
I take you
and whoever I feel fucking.
And whoever I'm calling.
BRANDY: Yeah.
ZACH: Okay.
ZACH: I am not cheating on you.
BRANDY: All you do is lie.
ZACH: Oh, I guess
I'm gonna pay for that too?
BRANDY: Yes. Get out!
ZACH: Hit me!
Hit me one more time?
Is everything okay in there?
ZACH: You got something
you wanna say, motherfucker?
You wanna
add to the conversation?
Open the door, bitch.
Let's talk.
We can talk all night.
I see you.
Fucking pussy.
[phone ringing]
Hey. Hi, Ruthie.
RUTHIE: Rian, baby. My star.
You finally made it up.
How's the room?
For a horror writing,
it's perfect.
[moaning]
BRANDY: Yes.
[rustling]
[bag thuds]
[upbeat music]
[upbeat music continues]
[sighs]
water rushing]
[grunts]
[man straining]
Hello?
Respond.
Dude, respond.
If you don't respond,
I'm gonna Narcan you.
Do you want me to Narcan you?
[keyboard clanking]
Are you okay?
[rapid exhales and inhales]
What's your name?
-Dan.
Stay with me, Dan.
Stay with me.
What did you do?
You are dying.
You are about to die.
-You are overjoyed.
-Why?
-[Dan panting]
-Hey. Hey. Stay with me.
-[panting]
-[taps]
Thanks.
What's your full name, Dan?
Stover.
Dan Stover.
You're good people.
Okay.
You're gonna be okay,
but you're not out of the woods.
I gotta bring you
to an ambulance.
[keyboard tapping]
I'm sorry
you had to deal with that.
Are you okay?
Hm?
That guy you helped,
that was a lot to deal with.
You must be upset.
Yeah. It's kind of my job.
We want our guests
to feel secure,
but it can be hard
with so many transients
coming through.
I'm kind of
a transient right now.
WOMAN ON TV:
Hector Allen Darbes
wanted for three counts
each of murder,
rape, and sexual abuse
of a corpse.
If you have any information
as to Mr. Darbes's whereabouts,
please inform
your local authorities.
The suspect is six feet tall...
He was my mailman.
...brown hair and brown eyes.
NAJA: He's been
all over the news...
with a 25,000-dollar reward.
You should leave a tip.
I called the cops,
like, six times.
Does that count?
NAJA: Should.
He's the reason I'm up here.
He would send me
other people's packages.
And when I called him on it,
he started trying to talk
all the time.
Just knocking up.
So, I made a complaint.
And they rerouted him.
And he started
sending me these weird...
letters.
By the end of it,
he was breaking into my house.
Just...
opening the door
and leaving it unlocked.
That's terrifying.
I just want him
to leave me the fuck alone.
Did you get a restraining order?
He threw a brick through
my window because of that.
NAJA: At least
they're looking for him now.
Hm.
Yeah.
All it took was three murders.
Just ring me for a room.
NAJA: Hey.
I'm sorry if what I said
didn't come out right.
It's okay.
I don't make
a lot of friends up here.
People come and go.
I make small talk.
Other than that,
words can be tricky.
It's fine, really.
What I should have said is...
I'm sorry you had
to go through all that.
If he's the reason
you're up here,
-I'm not charging your card.
-No. No.
I'm not trying to get out
of paying for a room.
-Okay?
-NAJA: No.
It's not about that.
I...
My husband...
he was kind of a tyrant.
It's already costing you
more than I'm willing to charge.
I know.
I appreciate that.
I don't always say
the right thing,
but I do it when I can.
[keyboard tapping]
[grunts, coughs]
Fuck.
This is Sarah.
You know what to do.
[phone beeps]
Hey.
I'm, I'm actually
at a motel bar.
Ah, I don't know
what I was gonna say,
but I started writing again,
and I don't know.
I, I based the main
character on you, like, loosely.
It's funny, though.
Like, real you isn't
really, like...
Oh, shit.
Really, you wasn't hunted
by a serial killer
that I know of.
Although, that would
explain the ghost thing.
VOICE RECORD:
When you have finished
recording, you may hang up
or press 1 for more options.
Just I wanted to let you know
what coup.
And, if you ever wanted to talk,
I'd, I'd really appreciate that.
I still love you.
All right.
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
Hello?
Is anybody in here?
Do I need, like,
a lifeguard or something?
[light buzzes]
[light switch clicks]
[thuds]
[water sloshes]
[phone rings]
Sorry. I didn't mean
to wake you.
I just wanted to talk.
BOSS: We can talk Monday.
Get some rest. Feel better.
I won't be in Monday.
BOSS: This is what? Four weeks?
KATIE: I'm dealing
with something, and I,
I just, I need more time.
BOSS: Katie, you remember
the girl who had that accident?
The one who was so high
that paramedics found her
tugging out her own fibula
because she thought
it was a car park
poking through her leg?
Zoe?
BOSS: Yeah, Zoe.
It takes a lot for Zoe
to show up every day.
And when her
addiction counselor
doesn't show for a month,
you know what she's thinking?
If my counselor doesn't care,
why should I?
I know.
But...
No, she's thinking,
"My reason for staying alive
called out... again."
[door clanks open]
[water sloshes]
What the fuck!
Did somebody take my clothes?
They're not expensive. Okay.
I'm a bargain shopper.
Burlington Coat Factory.
Target. Walmart.
Honestly, there's even some
fucking dollar tree in there.
I swear to God,
this is gonna take some,
I'm gonna fuck you up.
Who the fuck are you asshole?
[straining, grunting]
Sarah!
WOMAN: What brings you
to The Clayborn?
[whimpering]
Somebody help me, please!
KATIE: Are you okay?
[panting]
KATIE: Your pupils
are predilated.
Yeah. I, I get that a lot.
Sarah.
Sarah Getty.
I'm Katie.
Sorry.
What did you say
your name was again?
KATIE: Well, careful.
I think you hit your head.
Yeah.
You're Katie Waters.
[panting]
I need to get out of here.
Wait. Where are you going?
[panting]
What is this?
[bottles thud]
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
Jesus, fucking Christ.
[cell phone rings]
Sarah?
RUTHIE:
No. It's Ruthie, your agent.
You remember me?
Stop thinking
with your dick all the time.
Sorry.
I mean, good morning.
RUTHIE: Ah, It's four o'clock.
I couldn't sleep.
I had weird dreams all night.
RUTHIE: I hope that
doesn't get in the way.
Listen.
Let's get down to business.
We finally have a bite on
one of your ideas.
It's serious.
It won't.
Nightmares give me ideas.
RUTHIE: So, you're gonna
have a draft on Monday?
Ruthie, could I
pitch you something?
RUTHIE: Sure.
As long as
it's not stupid as fuck.
What if it wasn't
a horror story?
What if it was a romance?
[busy tone]
Hello? Ruthie?
[busy tone continues]
Bitch.
BRANDY: Oh, my god.
ZACH: Yeah.
[clatters]
[keyboard tapping]
BRANDY: Oh, my god, yes.
-[loud moaning]
-[keyboard tapping continues]
-[banging]
-BRANDY: Oh, Zach. Oh, yeah.
BRANDY: Oh, my god.
Right there.
-[banging intensifies]
-BRANDY: Yes. Yes.
[bottle clatter]
[moaning loudly]
[banging continues]
[Brandy moaning loudly]
-[moaning continues]
-[loud banging]
Oh, my god. Shut the fuck.
Can I get a room change?
Is there a problem
with your current room?
Yeah. The, neighbors...
they're indiscreet.
-I can ask them to keep it down.
-No.
I mean...
maybe there's another way.
You could upgrade
to the Presidential Suite
for 20 more dollars a day.
Is there a chance
I could downgrade?
All right.
That's better.
Let me know if I can
get you anything else.
Ah. Oh, thanks.
[door closes]
[beeps]
[thuds]
[suspenseful music]
[door clanks open]
[beeps]
[oven beeps]
[phone keypad tone]
[phone chimes]
Fuck.
Oh.
[sighs]
[clatters]
[groans]
[retches]
[retches, coughs]
[keyboard tapping]
[ominous music]
[screams]
WOMAN: No. Oh, my god.
Help!
No!
Somebody help me!
[keys clinking]
[squeals]
Who the fuck are you?
Where did you go?
Did anyone else see that?
A story you wrote came true?
Yes.
Like, in real time,
concurrently,
as I was writing it.
Listen, I know it sounds insane.
But there's no body.
RIAN: Is there something
wrong with this?
NAJA: Sometimes the feed
gets choppy.
My husband
used to take care of it
when he was still with us.
Where is he now?
Not with us.
That, that, that, that.
What, what was that?
Hard to say.
Oh, it's definitely something.
[telephone ringing]
[ringing continues]
Hello?
NAJA: Katie, This is Naja,
the property manager.
Is everything all right?
Yeah. Why?
NAJA: I just wanted
to make sure.
There's a guy here
talking crazy.
What guy?
NAJA: It's not Hector.
It's probably nothing.
I... Never mind.
Well, whoever it is, I didn't
tell anyone where I was going.
So, if he asks,
don't tell him I'm here.
No problem.
Seems pretty empty to me.
Look. Over here.
RIAN: It's blood.
That could be
from a small animal.
Care to confirm that theory?
Looks like it stopped bleeding.
Let's check her room.
-Check her room?
-Yeah.
I saw where she was staying.
RIAN: Let's see if she's there.
That's the room
you're talking about?
Listen, I know it sounds crazy.
I spent the whole day thinking
it was a fever dream myself,
but let's just
knock on her door.
Let's see if she answers.
NAJA: Maybe she's not in.
The lights are on.
She has the right to privacy.
-We should leave.
-RIAN: Why are you being
so weird?
What don't you want me to know?
[thuds]
That's the Richardson room.
The, the Richardson room?
Years ago, Scott Richardson
brought his family up here
on a ski trip.
They checked in,
and the next day,
the police found them massacred.
NAJA: All of them, except Scott.
He killed his wife
and three children.
But the thing of it, is that,
he said he didn't do it.
He said, all he did was write
down his intrusive thoughts...
and it all just
manifested that way.
What makes the stories
come true?
Richardson was a sick fuck
who murdered his family
and tried to blame the motel.
You said you're a writer.
Poetry.
Does it ever come true?
[cell phone rings]
Sarah?
RUTHIE:
No. It's not Sarah, dipshit.
Ah, you fucking wish.
Sorry.
I was expecting a call
from someone else.
What's up?
RUTHIE: You never
sent me a rough draft,
not even a chapter.
Ruthie...
I don't think
I can write anymore.
I met my protagonist.
The same name and everything.
RUTHIE: You listen here
shit for brains.
I get a producer
interested in your work
for the first time,
one with pockets, mind you,
and this is how you react?
Who's interested?
RUTHIE:
It doesn't fucking matter,
but it's a big amount.
Enough to get Sarah back.
Let's just say that.
Okay. I'm sorry, but fuck that.
Okay?
I can make it work.
I can do this.
RUTHIE:
Huh, do not fuck with me.
I can do this.
I can make it work.
RUTHIE: Oh, really?
Because a second ago,
you thought you were jigsaw.
Listen. I've been sweating
credit for, like, a year now.
I moved through
three different cities,
and I've quit, like,
two day jobs. I can do this.
RUTHIE: Did we just
have a breakthrough?
You're not
fucking with me, right?
No.
I'm gonna take your advice.
It's my story,
and it's time I control it.
[slow rock music]
[slow rock music continues]
[door closes]
[ominous music growing]
Shit.
[panting]
You think
he's here at the motel?
I don't know,
but it's pretty weird, right?
Definitely.
I don't mean to be dismissive.
-You've been through a lot.
-Okay.
But there were, like,
hundreds of letters out there.
And look at this.
They're all addressed to women.
And look at the date
on some of these.
I mean, some of these are old.
What do you want me
to do about it?
I don't know.
Call the cops,
get them to sweep the area.
NAJA: It's not that
I'm not convinced.
Okay. What about this?
What is it?
A bereavement letter
for a missing person.
What if these aren't random?
What if these are his victims?
NAJA: Ortiz.
O-R-T-I-Z.
Okay.
How about...
"Amanda Brown"?
NAJA: Spelled like it sounds.
The police say they don't
have any of these names
in their system.
How about Katie Waters?
K-A-T-I-E W-A-T-E-R-S.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
So, that's that?
The police is looking into it.
Where have I heard that before?
[envelopes rustle]
I really don't think
you should go.
We don't even know
that he's up here.
NAJA: At least here,
I can have your back
if it turns out he is.
Why should I believe that
if you don't believe me?
I do.
But if he wanted you
to have those letters,
maybe he wants you to run.
Maybe that's his plan.
His plan is to convince me
that it doesn't matter
where I go, or who I tell.
KATIE: Because no one
will actually do
anything about it,
'cause that's
every stalker's plan.
Well, if he followed you here,
he'll follow you there,
wherever there is.
Please don't go.
I'm just grabbing something.
[coughs]
Oh, hey.
You helped me out
by the pool the other day.
KATIE: Um, yeah. Hi.
I wanted to say,
I never
got a chance to thank you.
It was nothing.
I, I, I pretty much just
diagnosed your concussion
and then let you run away,
probably to go to sleep.
I wanted to ask, have you
noticed anything weird going on?
Yeah.
Why?
The night I fell...
I think
I might have been attacked.
Do you remember
what he looks like?
Does it mean anything to you?
More than you'd guess.
So, I'm not crazy.
That serial killer,
he's been stalking me...
and tormenting me.
And now I guess
he's noticed you too.
Holy shit.
Yeah. Sorry about that.
We should call the cops.
Yeah.
I've tried that a few times.
Well, we can't just do nothing.
I wasn't planning on it.
What do you have in mind?
This place is ancient.
I think this section's been
closed off for a while.
You really think he'll be here?
KATIE: Makes sense.
I mean...
it's pretty close.
And you wouldn't
have to check-in.
RIAN: True.
He could maneuver
the grounds pretty well too.
Or begin?
Here's good.
[door thuds, creaks]
Safe to say
he's not in this one?
What do we do if we find him?
Be ready.
[thunder rumbling]
KATIE: I recognize that.
Some of the gifts he sent me.
I threw it out.
RIAN: Whatever it is,
it smells rancid.
Lights out.
KATIE: You wanna tussle,
motherfucker?
Do it.
Open the door, right here!
No. That's what he wants!
He wants to fuck around
and find out.
Good. Let him.
No. It's a trap.
He wants you to go out there.
Let me go!
It's not worth it.
I know!
Let... me... go.
[thudding]
You leave me something?
Fuck you!
Get your refund, asshole.
Mint condition, never opened.
[breathes heavily]
KATIE: Thanks for that
back there.
RIAN: Are you kidding?
That was all you.
No. I mean, sometimes,
I just wanna get it over with,
whatever it is.
I was lucky I had someone
to pull me back, so, thanks.
I don't know.
I feel like I could have
done more.
He was right there.
You were fine.
What now?
I can't stay here.
You could stay in my room.
No, I mean the motel.
If you're gonna head out,
you could at least
let me walk you to your car.
Okay. Sure.
Perfect. I just gotta run
to the bathroom quick.
[keyboard tapping]
No. No. No.
No.
Fucking shit ass bitch. No!
No. No. No.
Oh, my god.
He slashed my fucking tires.
Fuck. Fuck.
What the fuck
did he do to my car?
Oh, fuck. Fuck.
Fuck me.
Fuck.
I know. It's really fucked up.
I do know a place we could go.
So, what do you think?
At least there's people around.
-Not great people, but...
-Hm.
There's only one bed.
I'll sleep on the floor.
I was thinking, ah,
whatever was in that package,
it smelled like rancid meat.
I doubt it was pork.
Exactly.
If it was, like, human remains
or something, we could use that.
People would take it seriously.
Whatever it is,
I'm not opening it.
Why not?
Because fuck him. That's why.
-I know. But...
-No.
No. You don't.
[sighs]
Because...
no one feels entitled
to your attention
or your body or your
whole fucking existence.
God, I have spent so much
of my time adjusting my life.
He can fuck himself
with a fucking chainsaw.
ZACH: Shut the fuck up.
-Stay out of it, man.
-I wasn't talking to you,
dickhead.
ZACH: Funny how it works out
one way for you
and another for me.
Get fucked.
ZACH: You wanna bark
like that all night?
Careful, bitch.
You won't get no pussy
pass for me.
Equal rights, equal fights.
-Oh, my god.
-Oh.
This is the last fucking
conversation we ever had.
-You understand me?
-Yeah, man.
WOMAN: Oh, my god. Are you okay?
Jesus Christ.
I hope that wasn't too much.
No. No.
If you're gonna do it,
that's the way you do it.
I can get the lights
if you're tired.
I'm not tired.
I, I didn't think you would be.
Get him anyways.
[cell phone vibrates]
How am I gonna
write you out of this?
[smooches]
You're literally me, dude.
Katie?
What's going on?
RIAN: We can write the future
however we want.
-KATIE: I trust you.
-What what's going on?
KATIE: You should come in.
RIAN: Help me.
Somebody help me.
Do you trust me? I don't know.
KATIE: You should come in.
Come on, Rian.
The water's warm.
You should come in.
-[squelches]
-[screaming]
Katie?
Sarah?
No!
[crying]
RIAN: Somebody help me!
I'm sorry.
No.
-[phone chimes]
-[panting]
[cell phone rings]
Ruthie?
RUTHIE: Oh, wow.
You got it right for once.
Now, where the fuck
is my draft, Rian?
RIAN: Yeah. Give me a second.
[groans] One second.
Ruthie, why the fuck did you
leave a million text messages
all freaking out?
RUTHIE:
Because today's the day
and my inbox is still empty.
Relax, okay?
I'll have everything
over to you by tonight.
[footsteps approaching]
[keyboard tapping]
MAN: I never said
you'd be alone.
For what it's worth,
this has nothing to do with you.
Did you change your mind?
It's okay if you wanna
get it over with.
[man exhales]
Oh, my god.
[chuckles] It's just you.
I think I know
where to find him.
I just gotta
grab something first.
[breathes heavily]
[screams]
-RIAN: It's okay.
-Here is the...
RIAN: It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
If he's in there, I need you
to go ham with that bear mace.
Spray the whole damn
fucking can. I don't care.
Don't worry.
I'll burn his fucking lungs out.
Whoa. Whoa.
Don't touch them, fingerprints.
RIAN: Holy fuck.
I've never been this close
to a dead body before.
Don't freak out.
She'll lick your pussy.
KATIE: Come on.
He'll be back any second.
This isn't right.
No shit.
I didn't write this.
KATIE: There he is.
I see you, motherfucker!
Hurry your ass up!
RIAN: Wait!
Hey. What are you doing?
Stop. Slow down.
Hey. Oh, darn.
The brick's are fucking heavy.
Yeah.
I'm not gonna
let you get yourself killed.
That's mine.
There's a right fucking way
to do this and the wrong one.
Get your fucking hands off me.
Emily. Emily.
Oh, you, have you seen my girl?
Look, you can just
forget about last night.
Okay? I, I just...
It was really unwarranted
you coming in like that,
but I could really use
your help right now
because I've been
looking everywhere,
but I can't find her.
I don't understand.
KATIE: It's a lot to process.
We should go look for her.
We can help her.
We already found her.
Well, that could've,
was probably somebody else.
Her father has her.
Oh, I know it.
I knew that piece of shit
would come back.
He's got her right now, he's,
he's taking her to his parents'.
He's...
Is there anything that
she always has on her?
A keepsake?
BRANDY: Her phone.
KATIE: Anything else
that we could identify her by,
that, if she doesn't
have her phone on her?
BRANDY: It's an Irish ring
with two hands
holding a heart with a crown.
For love, friendship,
and loyalty.
I'll go.
Go where?
I'll go get the pictures. Okay?
RUTHIE: Where's the
goddamn draft, Rian?
Things got a little
out of pocket, okay?
But I'm handling it.
RUTHIE:
What are you doing right now?
I'm writing.
RUTHIE:
It sounds like you're walking.
I'm casting out
a fucking plot hole, okay?
Leave me alone.
[thuds]
I'm sorry.
I didn't write this.
KATIE: Here.
Thanks.
Is she still there?
I don't think there's anything
we can do at this point.
I know, but,
we can't just leave her there.
I'm looking for her,
and I'm finding her.
And I'm gonna
take her away from this place.
[gasping]
Don't bullshit me.
I need to understand
why this is happening.
I told you it's a story.
Richardson made
all that shit up.
Naja, I wrote that
the cell towers went down
and I wrote
that the bridge collapsed.
I even wrote all those steps,
but I didn't write that girl
and now it's like
it's writing itself.
Why the fuck
am I losing control?
Maybe the story
has its own wealth.
I didn't do this.
He did it on his own. Yeah.
NAJA: What else
did he do on his own?
I need to go back to my laptop.
"Chapter one."
"Katie Waters was nice
to Hector Allen Darbes once."
"And he never
forgave her for it."
What the fuck?
Hello, police. Yes.
There's a guest here,
Rian Burman.
-He killed--
-Naja you're a fucking liar.
"If she'd just
opened his letters,
she'd have known that every gift
he'd left her was a heart
from someone she loved,
decorated in teeth,
and that he'd keep doing it
until she gave him
the attention he deserved."
I'm not gonna kill you.
I'm not gonna kill you. Okay?
I'm just gonna leave you here.
I'm just leaving you here.
Stop it.
Now, I already gave
your name to the police.
They'll be here within the hour.
No, they won't. Okay?
Now, the roads
and the bridge down.
Okay? He'll kill her by then.
I wrote a poem once
about my husband
driving our lives into
the ditch with this business,
about a car crash,
about him burning alive,
restrained in the fire.
That doesn't sound like
a fucking coincidence.
I didn't think so.
Not at first.
But I spent
years feeling guilty.
A murderer's guilt.
Why?
Because I wrote a poem?
The only thing I did
was speak my truth.
I didn't kill him.
Stop fucking lying to me.
You're wrong.
I'm sorry.
-Stay here.
-RIAN: But you're wrong.
Stay here.
NAJA: It'll be better for you
in the long run!
[door opens and closes]
NAJA: He tied me up.
He, he's gonna hurt somebody.
Can you untie me, please?
He, he was here a minute ago.
He's gonna hurt somebody.
I just need some help.
I called the police.
Are you just gonna stand here?
[groans]
I got the pictures.
Where's Brandy?
What the fuck is this?
I, I think I mentioned
I'm a writer.
"His love was a war
of attrition."
"He'd show her
what he was capable of."
-[thuds]
-[clatters]
What the fuck
is this shit, Rian?
It's iambic pentameter.
This is my trauma.
This is my life.
Why the fuck is it in your
computer under your name?
You're a character in my story.
I've been trying to help you.
I was never gonna let
anything bad happen to you.
You need to stay
the fuck away from me.
Listen, I'm sorry. Okay?
I know I should have
told you earlier. Okay?
You're insane.
Tonight,
Hector is gonna get you,
and I need to be with you
when that happens.
No!
Do you have any fucking idea
what you just did?
RIAN: And the stalker
wasn't far behind.
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
[heavy breathing]
Fuck?
STALKER: You're gonna
have to get a lot closer
if you wanna use that.
You remember your patient
Zoey from, from the clinic?
She really missed you
the past couple of days.
[screams]
Fuck you!
[whimpering]
-[rapid breathing]
-[grunting]
Stalker couldn't
have found it on.
Wasn't that Katie
would have help.
[grunting]
Take me in my fucking room.
STALKER: It's so hard.
I never did.
Change your mind.
You know, it's your turn.
Fuck you.
STALKER: Come on.
I'm gonna get some teeth.
That'll give you some time
to sober up and really think.
I mean, really think about it.
[choking]
[slow music playing]
Don't worry. I'm here.
[grunting]
[choking]
What are you doing?
Get off of him.
You're gonna kill him.
I thought we had
an understanding.
If you really believe
that you could learn to love me,
I think you could.
And you're gonna
have to prove it.
Brandy?
What are you doing here?
Come on. We get--
[gasps]
She's not going anywhere.
[panting]
[exhales] Oh.
I'm giving you a chance.
Do you still want it?
What do you need me to do?
Just want you to get in.
STALKER: All the way in.
I want you to soak with them.
I want you to remember them
if you ever think of leaving.
[chuckles]
Now, go under.
[thuds, splashes]
[panting]
[screams]
You drown in their
fucking blood!
Not me!
NAJA: Oh, good.
RIAN: You're okay.
Let's get you somewhere safe.
I'm so proud of you.
You finished the story.
That you put me through.
I know.
And it was wrong, but I'm
gonna make it up to you.
Do you trust me?
I trust you.
KATIE: What did you think was
gonna happen between us, Rian?
Like I said, we can have
any future we want.
Literally, any future we want.
KATIE: I'm not just
going to forget everything.
Could you just be quiet
for, like, two minutes?
I'm almost done.
[keyboard tapping]
Rian types.
Nah.
[screams]
What the fuck.
[gasps]
[straining]
I can change.
I don't want you to change.
Please write me
however you want.
I don't want anyone
you could ever be.
But I do want you to feel it.
[screaming]
["Miss Lonely" playing]
♪ I need to know ♪
♪ I need to know just
What you're looking for ♪
♪ And how you're gonna find
That it isn't me ♪
♪ You're looking for ♪
♪ You're looking for someone
To pick you up ♪
♪ And sweep you off your feet ♪
♪ Lonely
Going out again tonight ♪
♪ Searching for someone like
You did last week, last week ♪
♪ Oh, no, at least
You're tryin' ♪
♪ I kinda like the way
You waste your time ♪
♪ Don't go chasin' everybody ♪
♪ You need to look
A little closer ♪
♪ Maybe you can find me ♪
♪ I'm the one
You're looking for ♪
♪ I can be there
In a heart beat ♪
♪ No need to worry anymore ♪
♪ Your lonely days are over ♪
♪ Lonely, lonely
Days are over ♪
♪ You're making through it ♪
♪ You see that
Everyone was right about ♪
♪ The love of finding you ♪
♪ Yes, it's true ♪
♪ And I can do it ♪
♪ I could be everything
You'd ever need ♪
♪ And sweep you off your feet ♪
♪ Lonely, going out
Again tonight ♪
♪ Searching for someone like
You did last week, last week ♪
♪ Oh, no, at least
You're tryin' ♪
♪ I kinda like the way
You waste your time! ♪
♪ Don't go chasin' everybody ♪
♪ You need to look
A little closer ♪
♪ Maybe you can find me ♪
♪ I'm the one
You're looking for ♪
♪ I can be there
In a heart beat ♪
♪ No need to worry anymore ♪
♪ Your lonely days are over ♪
♪ Lonely, lonely
Days are over ♪
[music ends]